{
  "participantID": "93de7372-685b-40c4-84e9-01fd740a21b8",
  "demographicsAnswers": [
    {
      "participantID": "93de7372-685b-40c4-84e9-01fd740a21b8",
      "age": 38,
      "gender": "male",
      "experience": "more-three",
      "englishLevel": "advanced"
    }
  ],
  "score": 10,
  "questionData": {
    "question0": {
      "questionIndex": 0,
      "questionOrder": 1,
      "questionText": "wording change",
      "caseFormat": "camel4",
      "optionsGiven": [
        "wordingChange",
        "wordingChane",
        "wardingChange",
        "wordingChagne"
      ],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
      "selectedOption": "wordingChange",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "timeTaken": 7837.69999998808
    },
    "question1": {
      "questionIndex": 1,
      "questionOrder": 2,
      "questionText": "algorithm numbers",
      "caseFormat": "kebab2",
      "optionsGiven": [
        "algorithmn-numbers",
        "algorithm-nunbers",
        "algorithm-numbers",
        "algortithm-numbers"
      ],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
      "selectedOption": "algorithm-numbers",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "timeTaken": 4915.79999999702
    },
    "question2": {
      "questionIndex": 2,
      "questionOrder": 3,
      "questionText": "algorithm numbers",
      "caseFormat": "camel2",
      "optionsGiven": [
        "algorithmnNumbers",
        "algorithmNunbers",
        "algorithmNumbers",
        "algortithmNumbers"
      ],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
      "selectedOption": "algorithmNumbers",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "timeTaken": 3099.7000000029802
    },
    "question3": {
      "questionIndex": 3,
      "questionOrder": 4,
      "questionText": "query indexes",
      "caseFormat": "kebab3",
      "optionsGiven": [
        "querry-indexes",
        "query-inbexes",
        "query-indexes",
        "quary-indexes"
      ],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
      "selectedOption": "query-indexes",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "timeTaken": 4483.5
    },
    "question4": {
      "questionIndex": 4,
      "questionOrder": 5,
      "questionText": "packet size",
      "caseFormat": "kebab5",
      "optionsGiven": [
        "packets-size",
        "paket-Size",
        "packet-side",
        "packet-size"
      ],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
      "selectedOption": "packet-size",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "timeTaken": 3583.0999999940395
    },
    "question5": {
      "questionIndex": 5,
      "questionOrder": 6,
      "questionText": "packet size",
      "caseFormat": "camel5",
      "optionsGiven": [
        "packetSize",
        "paketSize",
        "packetsSize",
        "packetSide"
      ],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
      "selectedOption": "packetSize",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "timeTaken": 2216.4000000059605
    },
    "question6": {
      "questionIndex": 6,
      "questionOrder": 7,
      "questionText": "wording change",
      "caseFormat": "kebab4",
      "optionsGiven": [
        "wording-change",
        "wording-chagne",
        "wording-chane",
        "warding-change"
      ],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
      "selectedOption": "wording-change",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "timeTaken": 2399.5999999940395
    },
    "question7": {
      "questionIndex": 7,
      "questionOrder": 8,
      "questionText": "jump left",
      "caseFormat": "camel1",
      "optionsGiven": [
        "junpLeft",
        "jumnpLeft",
        "jumpLelt",
        "jumpLeft"
      ],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
      "selectedOption": "jumpLeft",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "timeTaken": 2966.4000000059605
    },
    "question8": {
      "questionIndex": 8,
      "questionOrder": 9,
      "questionText": "jump left",
      "caseFormat": "kebab1",
      "optionsGiven": [
        "jump-lelt",
        "jump-left",
        "junp-left",
        "junmp-left"
      ],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
      "selectedOption": "jump-left",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "timeTaken": 2599.5999999940395
    },
    "question9": {
      "questionIndex": 9,
      "questionOrder": 10,
      "questionText": "query indexes",
      "caseFormat": "camel3",
      "optionsGiven": [
        "querryIndexes",
        "queryInbexes",
        "queryIndexes",
        "quaryIndexes"
      ],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
      "selectedOption": "queryIndexes",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "timeTaken": 2890.5999999940395
    }
  }
}
